<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web3 on Welcome to the World of Web3</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/tags/web3/</link><description>Recent content in Web3 on Welcome to the World of Web3</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 21:00:49 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/tags/web3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aleo 零知识证明网络服务器节点搭建教程</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/aleo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 21:00:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/aleo/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="aleo简介">Aleo简介&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Aleo 致力于通过其创新平台为用户和应用程序开发人员提供前所未有的隐私保护。利用去中心化系统和零知识加密技术，Aleo 实现了网络上用户数据的绝对保密性。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>IO.NET GPU 显卡算力挖矿教程</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/io-net/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 19:26:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/io-net/</guid><description>&lt;p>IO.NET最近显卡资源出租挖矿模式比较火，后续也有空投可能，代币即将上线，今天说一下如何挖矿，首先支持Ubuntu Linux，MacOS和Windows操作系统，就以Windows为例讲解具体过程&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>本地搭建谷歌Google Gemini人工智能聊天机器人，GPT4完美替代品</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/gpt-4-gemini-pro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:57:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/gpt-4-gemini-pro/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="前言">前言&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>今天和大家说一下本地就能轻松搭建的谷歌Google Gemini Pro人工智能聊天机器人，可以作为GPT4完美替代品。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>前些天，Google也终于开放了Gemini Pro 的接口免费申请，现在Chatgpt4已经停止注册，所以之前没有注册的目前还无法体验最强大的人工智能工具，而且本身GPT4成本就比较高，所以大多数人还是用的GPT3.5，虽然本身非常棒，但有一个问题就是资料库并不是最新的，所以今天咱们一起研究一下如何搭建同样非常强大的，谷歌公司推出的Gemini Pro，最主要的是可以本地或者是云搭建，完全属于自己的AI玩具！&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Taiko Airdrop Tutorial</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid><description>&lt;p>Taiko is a Layer 2 solution based on Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s ZK-Rollup (Type 1 ZK-EVM). It can be considered a competitor to ZKSync. After successful testing in the first two phases, Taiko has now reached the Alpha3 phase, and it&amp;rsquo;s confirmed that tokens will be released in the future. This means that early participants might receive good rewards. In this guide, we will outline the specific steps for interaction, including basic interactions, contract deployment, and setting up nodes. By following this tutorial, you should be well-prepared for similar airdrop campaigns in the future.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Taiko 公链交互完全教程[明牌空投]</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid><description>&lt;p>Taiko是基于以太坊的ZK-Rollup (类型1 ZK-EVM)Layer2。算是ZKSync的竞品，经过了前两个阶段的测试，目前来到了Alpha3阶段，确认将来会发布代币，可以说是明牌空投了，所以在早期参与的用户回报应该会不错，这里就给大家整理一下具体的交互步骤，包括常规交互、部署合约和搭建节点，通过这一个教程，以后做这类空投应该也会触类旁通。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why and How to Diversify Global Asset Allocation</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/asset-allocation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:05:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/asset-allocation/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today, I got together with friends and had some insights to share, so let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the topic of global asset allocation. In the past, I simply outlined the concept to my friends, and within a little over a year, without really doing much, our assets appreciated by around 50%. Considering the current overall economic situation, that&amp;rsquo;s quite a decent achievement.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In today&amp;rsquo;s ever-changing economic landscape, why do we need to engage in global asset allocation? And how can we effectively allocate our assets to achieve appreciation and preservation in value?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>为何以及如何做全球资产配置</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/asset-allocation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:57:22 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/asset-allocation/</guid><description>&lt;p>今天和朋友聚了一下，有感而发，聊一下全球资产配置这个话题，因为之前只是简单给朋友规划了一下，也就一年多的时间，什么也没干，资产就增值了50%左右，再这样的一个整体经济形势下，应该算是个不错的成绩。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Open an Account of German Virtual Bank N26</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/n26/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:34:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/n26/</guid><description>&lt;p>As we all know, in the cryptocurrency world, handling deposits and withdrawals is an essential and often complex matter. Therefore, in the upcoming tutorials, I will be providing a series of guides to help you tackle this issue.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Today, let&amp;rsquo;s start by taking a look at N26 Bank, a virtual bank that offers streamlined services. We&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the registration and KYC process for N26.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Step 1: Register and Download the N26 App&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>如何注册德国虚拟银行 N26</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/n26/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:21:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/n26/</guid><description>&lt;p>如何注册德国虚拟银行 N26&lt;/p>
&lt;p>众所周知，在币圈，出入金是一件特别重要的事，而且还挺复杂的，所以呢接下来我会出一系列教程，去帮助大家解决这个问题&lt;/p>
&lt;p>今天首先来看一下这个N26银行，它其实是一个虚拟银行，我们一起看一下N26的注册及KYC流程&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Exploring Universal Basic Income (UBI) in the Web3 Era</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/what-is-ubi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:19:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/what-is-ubi/</guid><description>&lt;p>In an ever-evolving world fueled by technological advancements, the concept of Universal Basic Income (UBI) has gained prominence as a potential solution to address economic disparities and empower individuals. With the emergence of Web3 and blockchain technology, the possibilities for implementing UBI in a more efficient and inclusive manner have taken center stage. Let&amp;rsquo;s embark on a journey to understand what UBI is, its potential benefits, and how it intersects with the Web3 landscape.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>探索Web3时代的全民基本收入（UBI）</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/what-is-ubi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:12:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/what-is-ubi/</guid><description>&lt;p>在不断发展的技术进步推动下，全民基本收入（UBI）的概念已经成为解决经济差距、赋予个人权力的潜在解决方案。随着Web3和区块链技术的出现，实施更高效和包容性的UBI的可能性日益凸显。让我们踏上一段旅程，了解什么是UBI，其潜在的好处，以及它如何与Web3领域相交融。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Use Web3 for Security</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/web3-security/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/web3-security/</guid><description>&lt;p>Web3, also known as Web 3.0 or the decentralized web, refers to the next evolution of the internet that is built on decentralized technologies such as blockchain. Web3 is designed to enhance security and privacy by giving users more control over their data and reducing their dependence on centralized intermediaries.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here are some ways you can use Web3 for security:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Use decentralized applications (dApps): Decentralized applications run on the blockchain and are designed to be more secure than traditional web applications. When you use a dApp, you have control over your data, and it cannot be accessed by a centralized authority. Some popular dApps include MetaMask, MyEtherWallet, and Uniswap.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Earn Free Cryptos in Web3 - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>How to Earn Free Crypto in the Crypto World - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Every year, the crypto world sees numerous projects that make people around us rich. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a myth; it&amp;rsquo;s real. With minimal investment, you can get lucky and receive free tokens from projects. Compared to active trading, airdrops seem to offer lower risks and potentially higher rewards. So, what are these airdrops and how can you participate in them? Generally, it involves getting involved in the early stages of a project or community and receiving rewards from the project team at little or no cost. However, you need to be familiar with some basics and prepare some essential tools.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>币圈新人如何撸毛，2023撸空投指南</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>币圈每年都有很多项目，让身边人实现暴富神话，是的，不是传说，在几乎没有投入的情况下，简直就是天上撒币一般的幸运，相比交易这种体力活，撸毛似乎是个风险更低，回报有可能更多的行为，具体是什么行为呢？一般来说就是参与项目或社区的早期建设，然后以无成本或低成本获得项目方奖励，当然需要先了解一些基本的知识并准备一些基本工具。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>什么是多重签名钱包</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/multisig-wallet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/multisig-wallet/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="什么是多重签名钱包multisig-wallet">什么是多重签名钱包（Multisig Wallet）？&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Multisig表示多重签名，而多重签名是一种特定类型的数字签名，而此类型的签名将允许两个以上用户作为一组来签署文档。因此，多重签名则通过多个单一签名的组合来产生。现在多重签名技术已经应用于加密货币世界，而其实这一原理其实早在比特币诞生之前就存在了。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>致Web3创始人-想要取得成功，这28条原则应谨记</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/web328/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 03:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/web328/</guid><description>&lt;p>这是我在过去4年中，通过100多次对话和加密货币投资中提炼出的见解，关于 Web3 创始人的28条原则：&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>项目在精不在多，专注于一个项目并努力使它能够创造出10倍或更大的价值。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>什么是PoP</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/whatispop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 03:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/whatispop/</guid><description>&lt;p>参与证明（PoP）是一种相当未知的共识算法。尽管如此，已经有几个区块链使用了这种算法。要了解此类区块链的工作原理，首先要了解区块链共识算法的工作原理。我们将向您解释什么是参与证明以及这种共识算法是如何工作的。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Web 3.0 和区块链开发者路线图 — 循序渐进</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/web3development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/web3development/</guid><description>&lt;p>币圈最近重大事件比较多，沉寂多年的门头沟终于有下文了。可能会对比特币价格产生重大影响。 最新的消息，Mt. Gox 的还款日期再次推迟到 9 月中旬；之前定的是8 月下旬，门头沟要向交易平台被黑的客户支付超过 137,000 比特币 ( BTC )。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>什么是去中心化身份 DID(Decentralized ID)</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/whatisdid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 03:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/whatisdid/</guid><description>&lt;p>什么是去中心化身份(DID,Decentralized ID)？&lt;/p>
&lt;p>现在， 想象一下在不同的应用程序和平台之间移动时不必每次都登录。想象一下，不检查您的手机进行双重身份验证。想象一下，不必担心数据泄露的不可避免性。随着我们从 Web2 迁移到 Web3，去中心化身份解决方案提供了一个无缝体验的网关，用户可以轻松安全地在不同平台之间穿梭。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>什么是Web3.0？是骗局还是机会？和中国有关系吗？</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/whatisweb3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/whatisweb3/</guid><description>&lt;p>今天聊一个有意思的话题，web3.0是什么？
我会用最简单易懂的话去介绍web3.0，保证每个人都能听懂。
首先我就结合我个人的从业经历，聊一下web1.0-3.0进化路径&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>什么是DYOR</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/whatisdyor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/whatisdyor/</guid><description>&lt;p>DYOR 是Do Your Own Research 的缩写，也就是做你自己的研究，这是币圈基本生存法则。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>我们鼓励所有新进入币圈的朋友，在投资之前研究和了解加密货币，以便能够准确地回答购买该货币并支持该项目的原因。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>小火箭节点2023最新使用教程</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/shadowsocks2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/shadowsocks2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>小火箭节点2023最新使用教程 | 小火箭节点二维码 | 小火箭节点订阅 | 小火箭节点购买 | 小火箭节点分享 | 小火箭节点配置&lt;/p>
&lt;p>小火箭指的是iOS系统上的代理软件ShadowRocket，需要用美区appleid购买下载，但是本身只是一个工具，并无内置节点，所以需要导入节点才可以正常使用。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>2023币安支持的国家</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/binance2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/binance2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>币安（Binance）是一家全球性的加密货币交易所，为超过100种加密货币提供交易平台。2018年初以来，币安在交易量方面被认为是全世界上最大的加密货币交易所。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is MEV</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/whatismev/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/whatismev/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today we will talk about what is MEV, which stands for Maximal Extractable Value, also known as maximizing profits on the Ethereum blockchain.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With the popularity of cryptocurrencies, Ethereum has become one of the most popular blockchains. MEV refers to the maximum value obtained through transactions on the Ethereum network. This value comes from operations such as flash loans, arbitrage, and price manipulation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In Ethereum transactions, miners can obtain MEV profits by reordering and packaging transactions. For example, they can buy relevant tokens before the transaction and sell them after the transaction, profiting from the price difference.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>