<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Airdrop on Welcome to the World of Web3</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/tags/airdrop/</link><description>Recent content in Airdrop on Welcome to the World of Web3</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.bitbitking.com/en/tags/airdrop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Taiko Airdrop Tutorial</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid><description>&lt;p>Taiko is a Layer 2 solution based on Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s ZK-Rollup (Type 1 ZK-EVM). It can be considered a competitor to ZKSync. After successful testing in the first two phases, Taiko has now reached the Alpha3 phase, and it&amp;rsquo;s confirmed that tokens will be released in the future. This means that early participants might receive good rewards. In this guide, we will outline the specific steps for interaction, including basic interactions, contract deployment, and setting up nodes. By following this tutorial, you should be well-prepared for similar airdrop campaigns in the future.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Earn Free Cryptos in Web3 - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>How to Earn Free Crypto in the Crypto World - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Every year, the crypto world sees numerous projects that make people around us rich. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a myth; it&amp;rsquo;s real. With minimal investment, you can get lucky and receive free tokens from projects. Compared to active trading, airdrops seem to offer lower risks and potentially higher rewards. So, what are these airdrops and how can you participate in them? Generally, it involves getting involved in the early stages of a project or community and receiving rewards from the project team at little or no cost. However, you need to be familiar with some basics and prepare some essential tools.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>