<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ens on Welcome to the World of Web3</title>
    <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ens on Welcome to the World of Web3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Taiko Airdrop Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid>
      <description>Taiko is a Layer 2 solution based on Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s ZK-Rollup (Type 1 ZK-EVM). It can be considered a competitor to ZKSync. After successful testing in the first two phases, Taiko has now reached the Alpha3 phase, and it&amp;rsquo;s confirmed that tokens will be released in the future. This means that early participants might receive good rewards. In this guide, we will outline the specific steps for interaction, including basic interactions, contract deployment, and setting up nodes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why and How to Diversify Global Asset Allocation</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/asset-allocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:05:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/asset-allocation/</guid>
      <description>Today, I got together with friends and had some insights to share, so let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the topic of global asset allocation. In the past, I simply outlined the concept to my friends, and within a little over a year, without really doing much, our assets appreciated by around 50%. Considering the current overall economic situation, that&amp;rsquo;s quite a decent achievement.&#xA;In today&amp;rsquo;s ever-changing economic landscape, why do we need to engage in global asset allocation?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open an Account of German Virtual Bank N26</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/n26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:34:53 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/n26/</guid>
      <description>As we all know, in the cryptocurrency world, handling deposits and withdrawals is an essential and often complex matter. Therefore, in the upcoming tutorials, I will be providing a series of guides to help you tackle this issue.&#xA;Today, let&amp;rsquo;s start by taking a look at N26 Bank, a virtual bank that offers streamlined services. We&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the registration and KYC process for N26.&#xA;Step 1: Register and Download the N26 App</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Universal Basic Income (UBI) in the Web3 Era</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/what-is-ubi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:19:15 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/what-is-ubi/</guid>
      <description>In an ever-evolving world fueled by technological advancements, the concept of Universal Basic Income (UBI) has gained prominence as a potential solution to address economic disparities and empower individuals. With the emergence of Web3 and blockchain technology, the possibilities for implementing UBI in a more efficient and inclusive manner have taken center stage. Let&amp;rsquo;s embark on a journey to understand what UBI is, its potential benefits, and how it intersects with the Web3 landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:58:21 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/contact/</guid>
      <description> Youtube WOW Twitter Email </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:39:26 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/about/</guid>
      <description> Cryptos Blockchains Web3 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to withdraw quickly and avoid OTC risks.</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/onecard2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/onecard2023/</guid>
      <description>Withdrawals are now worry-free! Take advantage of the current opportunity and get yourself a virtual credit card.&#xA;For those who previously couldn&amp;rsquo;t register due to server issues, you can try again now as registration is open.&#xA;This virtual credit card is usable in Mainland China, supporting Alipay, WeChat Pay, and more, with no or minimal transaction fees for small amounts.&#xA;To begin, log in with your Google account.&#xA;Fill in your information, and a QR code will appear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Web3 for Security</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/web3-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/web3-security/</guid>
      <description>Web3, also known as Web 3.0 or the decentralized web, refers to the next evolution of the internet that is built on decentralized technologies such as blockchain. Web3 is designed to enhance security and privacy by giving users more control over their data and reducing their dependence on centralized intermediaries.&#xA;Here are some ways you can use Web3 for security:&#xA;Use decentralized applications (dApps): Decentralized applications run on the blockchain and are designed to be more secure than traditional web applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Earn Free Cryptos in Web3 - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid>
      <description>How to Earn Free Crypto in the Crypto World - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023&#xA;Every year, the crypto world sees numerous projects that make people around us rich. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a myth; it&amp;rsquo;s real. With minimal investment, you can get lucky and receive free tokens from projects. Compared to active trading, airdrops seem to offer lower risks and potentially higher rewards. So, what are these airdrops and how can you participate in them?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I get a referral/invitation code for a Pi network?</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/pi-network-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/pi-network-2023/</guid>
      <description>How do I get a referral/invitation code for a Pi network? Does it work? How do I get an invitation code for pi? Pi Network Invitation code is BitBitKing .&#xA;Put - BitBitKing - as your invitation code in Pi Network and get 1 PI for free!&#xA;https://tinyurl.com/Pi-NetWork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is MEV</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/whatismev/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/whatismev/</guid>
      <description>Today we will talk about what is MEV, which stands for Maximal Extractable Value, also known as maximizing profits on the Ethereum blockchain.&#xA;With the popularity of cryptocurrencies, Ethereum has become one of the most popular blockchains. MEV refers to the maximum value obtained through transactions on the Ethereum network. This value comes from operations such as flash loans, arbitrage, and price manipulation.&#xA;In Ethereum transactions, miners can obtain MEV profits by reordering and packaging transactions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
