<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Welcome to the World of Web3</title>
        <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome to the World of Web3</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 05:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>How to withdraw quickly and avoid OTC risks.</title>
            <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/onecard2023/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/onecard2023/</guid>
            <description>Withdrawals are now worry-free! Take advantage of the current opportunity and get yourself a virtual credit card.
For those who previously couldn&amp;rsquo;t register due to server issues, you can try again now as registration is open.
This virtual credit card is usable in Mainland China, supporting Alipay, WeChat Pay, and more, with no or minimal transaction fees for small amounts.
To begin, log in with your Google account.
Fill in your information, and a QR code will appear.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Withdrawals are now worry-free! Take advantage of the current opportunity and get yourself a virtual credit card.</p>
<p>For those who previously couldn&rsquo;t register due to server issues, you can try again now as registration is open.</p>
<p>This virtual credit card is usable in Mainland China, supporting Alipay, WeChat Pay, and more, with no or minimal transaction fees for small amounts.</p>
<p>To begin, log in with your Google account.</p>
<p><img src="https://mirror.xyz/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimages.mirror-media.xyz%2Fpublication-images%2FSebOnLqL_vKLfBKG_0s-o.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75" alt="Image 1"></p>
<p><img src="https://mirror.xyz/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimages.mirror-media.xyz%2Fpublication-images%2Ft9EPmkGSEXZLmapf6haSA.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75" alt="Image 2"></p>
<p><img src="https://mirror.xyz/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimages.mirror-media.xyz%2Fpublication-images%2FpfHY_1s5IXaGUy_dy8EAl.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75" alt="Image 3"></p>
<p>Fill in your information, and a QR code will appear. Scan it with WeChat, record a short video for KYC purposes, and then wait a few minutes for the process to complete.</p>
<p>Referral code: 3AC16B</p>
<p>Currently, registration is by invitation only: <a href="http://bit.ly/bbkonekey">http://bit.ly/bbkonekey</a></p>
<p>For detailed instructions and usage, watch: <a href="https://youtu.be/-4qxLaCEQF0">https://youtu.be/-4qxLaCEQF0</a></p>
<p>Detailed registration tutorial: <a href="http://bit.ly/bbk-tools-Featured">http://bit.ly/bbk-tools-Featured</a></p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>How do I get a referral/invitation code for a Pi network?</title>
            <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/pi-network-2023/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/pi-network-2023/</guid>
            <description>How do I get a referral/invitation code for a Pi network? Does it work? How do I get an invitation code for pi? Pi Network Invitation code is BitBitKing .
Put - BitBitKing - as your invitation code in Pi Network and get 1 PI for free!
https://tinyurl.com/Pi-NetWork</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How do I get a referral/invitation code for a Pi network? Does it work? How do I get an invitation code for pi? Pi Network Invitation code is BitBitKing .</p>
<p>Put - BitBitKing - as your invitation code in Pi Network and get 1 PI for free!</p>
<p><a href="https://tinyurl.com/Pi-NetWork">https://tinyurl.com/Pi-NetWork</a></p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>What is MEV</title>
            <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/whatismev/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/whatismev/</guid>
            <description>Today we will talk about what is MEV, which stands for Maximal Extractable Value, also known as maximizing profits on the Ethereum blockchain.
With the popularity of cryptocurrencies, Ethereum has become one of the most popular blockchains. MEV refers to the maximum value obtained through transactions on the Ethereum network. This value comes from operations such as flash loans, arbitrage, and price manipulation.
In Ethereum transactions, miners can obtain MEV profits by reordering and packaging transactions.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today we will talk about what is MEV, which stands for Maximal Extractable Value, also known as maximizing profits on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p>With the popularity of cryptocurrencies, Ethereum has become one of the most popular blockchains. MEV refers to the maximum value obtained through transactions on the Ethereum network. This value comes from operations such as flash loans, arbitrage, and price manipulation.</p>
<p>In Ethereum transactions, miners can obtain MEV profits by reordering and packaging transactions. For example, they can buy relevant tokens before the transaction and sell them after the transaction, profiting from the price difference.</p>
<p>Additionally, flash loans are another form of MEV. Flash loans involve borrowing and trading to complete transactions within seconds, resulting in significant profits in the market. This operation needs to be completed quickly and before the transaction is confirmed. Miners can gain MEV profits by rapidly packaging flash loan transactions.</p>
<p>Furthermore, there is a method called &ldquo;manipulation&rdquo; where traders buy a token during a transaction and then sell it in the same transaction. This can make other traders believe that the token&rsquo;s price is dropping, leading them to sell in large quantities to manipulate the price. Miners can earn MEV profits by collecting fees from these transactions.</p>
<p>In conclusion, MEV is a new way of earning on the Ethereum network, and it requires miners to perform specific operations to obtain profits. I hope this video helps you better understand the concept of MEV.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
