<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Welcome to the World of Web3</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome to the World of Web3</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:19:15 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring Universal Basic Income (UBI) in the Web3 Era</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/what-is-ubi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:19:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/what-is-ubi/</guid><description>In an ever-evolving world fueled by technological advancements, the concept of Universal Basic Income (UBI) has gained prominence as a potential solution to address economic disparities and empower individuals. With the emergence of Web3 and blockchain technology, the possibilities for implementing UBI in a more efficient and inclusive manner have taken center stage. Let&amp;rsquo;s embark on a journey to understand what UBI is, its potential benefits, and how it intersects with the Web3 landscape.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In an ever-evolving world fueled by technological advancements, the concept of Universal Basic Income (UBI) has gained prominence as a potential solution to address economic disparities and empower individuals. With the emergence of Web3 and blockchain technology, the possibilities for implementing UBI in a more efficient and inclusive manner have taken center stage. Let&rsquo;s embark on a journey to understand what UBI is, its potential benefits, and how it intersects with the Web3 landscape.</p>
<h3 id="what-is-ubi">What is UBI?</h3>
<p>At its core, Universal Basic Income is a revolutionary idea that suggests every citizen of a nation should receive a regular and unconditional payment from the government, regardless of their income, employment status, or other factors. Imagine a world where individuals have a safety net, a financial cushion that ensures their basic needs are met, allowing them to pursue their passions, education, and entrepreneurial endeavors without the fear of poverty.</p>
<h3 id="the-web3-revolution">The Web3 Revolution</h3>
<p>Enter Web3, a decentralized and user-centric internet powered by blockchain technology. Web3 aims to reshape the digital landscape, giving users greater control over their data and online experiences. Blockchain, a fundamental technology behind Web3, offers transparency, security, and trust through its decentralized nature.</p>
<h3 id="synergy-between-ubi-and-web3">Synergy Between UBI and Web3</h3>
<p>UBI and Web3 may seem like unlikely companions, but they share a common vision: empowerment of individuals. Through blockchain&rsquo;s transparent and tamper-proof nature, UBI distribution could be more efficient, ensuring that funds reach the intended recipients without intermediaries. Smart contracts, programmable code on the blockchain, could automate UBI payments, reducing administrative costs and ensuring fairness.</p>
<h3 id="decentralization-and-trust">Decentralization and Trust</h3>
<p>One of the key challenges in implementing UBI is ensuring that funds are distributed fairly and transparently. Web3&rsquo;s decentralized architecture could provide the solution. Smart contracts can be coded to allocate UBI based on predefined criteria, leaving no room for bias or manipulation. This not only enhances transparency but also builds trust among citizens, as they can verify the distribution process.</p>
<h3 id="digital-identity-and-inclusivity">Digital Identity and Inclusivity</h3>
<p>Web3 introduces the concept of self-sovereign digital identities, allowing individuals to control their personal data securely. This aligns perfectly with UBI&rsquo;s requirement to accurately identify recipients. Blockchain-based digital identities could enable governments to ensure UBI reaches the right people while protecting their privacy.</p>
<h3 id="challenges-and-considerations">Challenges and Considerations</h3>
<p>As promising as the UBI-Web3 marriage sounds, challenges persist. Technological literacy, infrastructure, and regulatory frameworks need to be in place for seamless implementation. Additionally, concerns about potential misuse of UBI funds, scalability of blockchain networks, and the digital divide must be addressed.</p>
<h3 id="a-new-frontier-of-economic-empowerment">A New Frontier of Economic Empowerment</h3>
<p>In the Web3 era, Universal Basic Income takes on a new form, leveraging blockchain&rsquo;s capabilities to create a more equitable and transparent society. It envisions a future where economic empowerment is democratized, and individuals are free to explore their passions, education, and entrepreneurial pursuits without the constraints of financial insecurity. As we navigate the intersection of UBI and Web3, one thing becomes clear: the potential for positive change is boundless.</p>
<h3 id="conclusion">Conclusion</h3>
<p>UBI and Web3 represent two transformative ideas that converge to reshape our world. By harnessing the power of blockchain and decentralized technologies, UBI could become a reality that empowers individuals, reduces inequalities, and fosters a stronger sense of community. As we move forward, it&rsquo;s essential to embrace the possibilities and address the challenges, paving the way for a future where economic well-being is accessible to all.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>How to withdraw quickly and avoid OTC risks.</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/onecard2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/onecard2023/</guid><description>Withdrawals are now worry-free! Take advantage of the current opportunity and get yourself a virtual credit card.
For those who previously couldn&amp;rsquo;t register due to server issues, you can try again now as registration is open.
This virtual credit card is usable in Mainland China, supporting Alipay, WeChat Pay, and more, with no or minimal transaction fees for small amounts.
To begin, log in with your Google account.
Fill in your information, and a QR code will appear.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Withdrawals are now worry-free! Take advantage of the current opportunity and get yourself a virtual credit card.</p>
<p>For those who previously couldn&rsquo;t register due to server issues, you can try again now as registration is open.</p>
<p>This virtual credit card is usable in Mainland China, supporting Alipay, WeChat Pay, and more, with no or minimal transaction fees for small amounts.</p>
<p>To begin, log in with your Google account.</p>
<p><img src="https://mirror.xyz/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimages.mirror-media.xyz%2Fpublication-images%2FSebOnLqL_vKLfBKG_0s-o.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75" alt="Image 1"></p>
<p><img src="https://mirror.xyz/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimages.mirror-media.xyz%2Fpublication-images%2Ft9EPmkGSEXZLmapf6haSA.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75" alt="Image 2"></p>
<p><img src="https://mirror.xyz/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fimages.mirror-media.xyz%2Fpublication-images%2FpfHY_1s5IXaGUy_dy8EAl.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75" alt="Image 3"></p>
<p>Fill in your information, and a QR code will appear. Scan it with WeChat, record a short video for KYC purposes, and then wait a few minutes for the process to complete.</p>
<p>Referral code: 3AC16B</p>
<p>Currently, registration is by invitation only: <a href="http://bit.ly/bbkonekey">http://bit.ly/bbkonekey</a></p>
<p>For detailed instructions and usage, watch: <a href="https://youtu.be/-4qxLaCEQF0">https://youtu.be/-4qxLaCEQF0</a></p>
<p>Detailed registration tutorial: <a href="http://bit.ly/bbk-tools-Featured">http://bit.ly/bbk-tools-Featured</a></p>
]]></content></item><item><title>How to Use Web3 for Security</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/web3-security/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/web3-security/</guid><description>Web3, also known as Web 3.0 or the decentralized web, refers to the next evolution of the internet that is built on decentralized technologies such as blockchain. Web3 is designed to enhance security and privacy by giving users more control over their data and reducing their dependence on centralized intermediaries.
Here are some ways you can use Web3 for security:
Use decentralized applications (dApps): Decentralized applications run on the blockchain and are designed to be more secure than traditional web applications.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Web3, also known as Web 3.0 or the decentralized web, refers to the next evolution of the internet that is built on decentralized technologies such as blockchain. Web3 is designed to enhance security and privacy by giving users more control over their data and reducing their dependence on centralized intermediaries.</p>
<p>Here are some ways you can use Web3 for security:</p>
<p>Use decentralized applications (dApps): Decentralized applications run on the blockchain and are designed to be more secure than traditional web applications. When you use a dApp, you have control over your data, and it cannot be accessed by a centralized authority. Some popular dApps include MetaMask, MyEtherWallet, and Uniswap.</p>
<p>Use a hardware wallet: A hardware wallet is a physical device that stores your private keys offline, making it less vulnerable to hacking or theft. When you use a hardware wallet, you can securely store your cryptocurrencies and access them only when needed.</p>
<p>Use a decentralized exchange (DEX): A decentralized exchange allows you to trade cryptocurrencies without the need for a centralized intermediary. When you use a DEX, you have control over your funds, and they cannot be accessed by a centralized authority. Some popular DEXs include Uniswap, Sushiswap, and Pancakeswap.</p>
<p>Verify the authenticity of smart contracts: Smart contracts are self-executing contracts that run on the blockchain. When you use a smart contract, you want to be sure that it is authentic and has not been tampered with. You can verify the authenticity of a smart contract by checking its code on the blockchain.</p>
<p>Use a VPN: A VPN (virtual private network) can help protect your privacy and security by encrypting your internet traffic and hiding your IP address. When you use a VPN, your internet service provider (ISP) cannot see what you are doing online, and your online activity is less vulnerable to hacking or surveillance.</p>
<p>Overall, Web3 offers many opportunities for enhancing security and privacy. By using decentralized technologies such as blockchain, you can have more control over your data and reduce your dependence on centralized intermediaries.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>How to Earn Free Cryptos in Web3 - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid><description>How to Earn Free Crypto in the Crypto World - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023
Every year, the crypto world sees numerous projects that make people around us rich. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a myth; it&amp;rsquo;s real. With minimal investment, you can get lucky and receive free tokens from projects. Compared to active trading, airdrops seem to offer lower risks and potentially higher rewards. So, what are these airdrops and how can you participate in them?</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How to Earn Free Crypto in the Crypto World - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023</p>
<p>Every year, the crypto world sees numerous projects that make people around us rich. It&rsquo;s not just a myth; it&rsquo;s real. With minimal investment, you can get lucky and receive free tokens from projects. Compared to active trading, airdrops seem to offer lower risks and potentially higher rewards. So, what are these airdrops and how can you participate in them? Generally, it involves getting involved in the early stages of a project or community and receiving rewards from the project team at little or no cost. However, you need to be familiar with some basics and prepare some essential tools.</p>
<p>Tools:</p>
<ol>
<li>Firstly, believe in science. If you don&rsquo;t understand the technology, you&rsquo;ll be left in the dark.</li>
<li>A Google account. It&rsquo;s not easy to register, so secure one when possible and maintain it well.</li>
<li>Twitter, often referred to as a copycat of Weibo. Maintain at least one actively, who knows, it might go viral.</li>
<li>Telegram, the place where scams abound. Don&rsquo;t trust any information blindly, but you should have one just in case.</li>
<li>Metamask, the essential browser wallet in the crypto world.</li>
<li>Mobile wallets like Trust, imToken, TP, etc. Make sure you download the genuine ones to avoid counterfeits.</li>
<li>Overseas app stores, such as an overseas Apple ID for iOS or a Google Play ID for Android. Note that they must be the international versions.</li>
<li>If you have multiple accounts, consider using multiple IP addresses and fingerprint browsers.</li>
<li>For those not fluent in English, use Chrome with translation or dictionary software.</li>
</ol>
<p>Wallet Accounts:
The security of your wallet is of utmost importance, even for seasoned players, as even the most experienced can fall victim to scams.</p>
<ol>
<li>Wallet software, such as the apps mentioned earlier, Metamask, or even hardware wallets for large assets, or multi-signature wallets.</li>
<li>Generating wallet addresses. Pay close attention to this, as you could become the target of others. Check out my previous videos for details. Separate the wallets you regularly use from those used for airdrops. Prepare hundreds of addresses primarily for ETH/BSC, and a few dozen for other mainnets, depending on the situation.</li>
<li>Keys and mnemonic phrases are critical; never take them lightly. Avoid taking screenshots or storing them on cloud storage. Pay extra attention to security if you&rsquo;re using an Android device. Physical storage is the most secure method.</li>
</ol>
<p>Testing Networks:
Set up mainstream EVM networks, including common test networks like Ropsten, Kovan, Goerli, etc. Chainlist is recommended for easy configuration. If you&rsquo;re unwilling to pay gas fees, participating in test networks is a good option. Many projects reward participants in test networks, and if a project becomes popular, the returns can be substantial.</p>
<p>Information:
In the crypto world, information is vital, and there are countless ways to access it. Whether you&rsquo;re good with RSS feeds, indexing, or following KOLs in specific fields, it&rsquo;s crucial to stay informed. I have also organized and categorized various tools and projects, and I will continue to update them periodically.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Crypto Tools Kit: <a href="https://bit.ly/Crypto-Tools">https://bit.ly/Crypto-Tools</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Tools Kit Featured: <a href="http://bit.ly/bbk-tools-Featured">http://bit.ly/bbk-tools-Featured</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Credit Cards: <a href="http://bit.ly/bbkonekey">http://bit.ly/bbkonekey</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Web3-Crypto Community: <a href="http://bit.ly/wow3-group">http://bit.ly/wow3-group</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Crypto Exchanges: <a href="https://bit.ly/Crypto-Exchanges">https://bit.ly/Crypto-Exchanges</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Fingerprint Browsers: <a href="http://bit.ly/bbkadsexplorer">http://bit.ly/bbkadsexplorer</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>IP Pools: <a href="https://tinyurl.com/ip-proxy">https://tinyurl.com/ip-proxy</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Nodes: <a href="https://tinyurl.com/wgetcloud">https://tinyurl.com/wgetcloud</a> or <a href="https://bit.ly/bbk-lightning-vpn">https://bit.ly/bbk-lightning-vpn</a></p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content></item><item><title>How do I get a referral/invitation code for a Pi network?</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/pi-network-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/pi-network-2023/</guid><description>How do I get a referral/invitation code for a Pi network? Does it work? How do I get an invitation code for pi? Pi Network Invitation code is BitBitKing .
Put - BitBitKing - as your invitation code in Pi Network and get 1 PI for free!
https://tinyurl.com/Pi-NetWork</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How do I get a referral/invitation code for a Pi network? Does it work? How do I get an invitation code for pi? Pi Network Invitation code is BitBitKing .</p>
<p>Put - BitBitKing - as your invitation code in Pi Network and get 1 PI for free!</p>
<p><a href="https://tinyurl.com/Pi-NetWork">https://tinyurl.com/Pi-NetWork</a></p>
]]></content></item><item><title>What is MEV</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/whatismev/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 03:15:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/en/posts/whatismev/</guid><description>Today we will talk about what is MEV, which stands for Maximal Extractable Value, also known as maximizing profits on the Ethereum blockchain.
With the popularity of cryptocurrencies, Ethereum has become one of the most popular blockchains. MEV refers to the maximum value obtained through transactions on the Ethereum network. This value comes from operations such as flash loans, arbitrage, and price manipulation.
In Ethereum transactions, miners can obtain MEV profits by reordering and packaging transactions.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today we will talk about what is MEV, which stands for Maximal Extractable Value, also known as maximizing profits on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p>With the popularity of cryptocurrencies, Ethereum has become one of the most popular blockchains. MEV refers to the maximum value obtained through transactions on the Ethereum network. This value comes from operations such as flash loans, arbitrage, and price manipulation.</p>
<p>In Ethereum transactions, miners can obtain MEV profits by reordering and packaging transactions. For example, they can buy relevant tokens before the transaction and sell them after the transaction, profiting from the price difference.</p>
<p>Additionally, flash loans are another form of MEV. Flash loans involve borrowing and trading to complete transactions within seconds, resulting in significant profits in the market. This operation needs to be completed quickly and before the transaction is confirmed. Miners can gain MEV profits by rapidly packaging flash loan transactions.</p>
<p>Furthermore, there is a method called &ldquo;manipulation&rdquo; where traders buy a token during a transaction and then sell it in the same transaction. This can make other traders believe that the token&rsquo;s price is dropping, leading them to sell in large quantities to manipulate the price. Miners can earn MEV profits by collecting fees from these transactions.</p>
<p>In conclusion, MEV is a new way of earning on the Ethereum network, and it requires miners to perform specific operations to obtain profits. I hope this video helps you better understand the concept of MEV.</p>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>