<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Airdrop on Welcome to the World of Web3</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/tags/airdrop/</link><description>Recent content in Airdrop on Welcome to the World of Web3</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/tags/airdrop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Taiko Airdrop Tutorial</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid><description>&lt;p>Taiko is a Layer 2 solution based on Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s ZK-Rollup (Type 1 ZK-EVM). It can be considered a competitor to ZKSync. After successful testing in the first two phases, Taiko has now reached the Alpha3 phase, and it&amp;rsquo;s confirmed that tokens will be released in the future. This means that early participants might receive good rewards. In this guide, we will outline the specific steps for interaction, including basic interactions, contract deployment, and setting up nodes. By following this tutorial, you should be well-prepared for similar airdrop campaigns in the future.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Taiko 公链交互完全教程[明牌空投]</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid><description>&lt;p>Taiko是基于以太坊的ZK-Rollup (类型1 ZK-EVM)Layer2。算是ZKSync的竞品，经过了前两个阶段的测试，目前来到了Alpha3阶段，确认将来会发布代币，可以说是明牌空投了，所以在早期参与的用户回报应该会不错，这里就给大家整理一下具体的交互步骤，包括常规交互、部署合约和搭建节点，通过这一个教程，以后做这类空投应该也会触类旁通。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OKX lifeform 空投教程</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/okx-lifeform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:48:27 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/okx-lifeform/</guid><description>&lt;p>Lifeform空投和OKX欧易合作了，直接上干货：&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>没OKX交易所的下载，还可以领盲盒，有的把APP更新到最新版本：
&lt;a href="https://tinyurl.com/Okx2022">https://tinyurl.com/Okx2022&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>最上方点击Web3钱包，没有的可以创建一个无私钥钱包，然后下面点击「发现」 到推荐频道，可以看到Cryptopedia里面第一个就是Lifeform的空投，不是的往后面划一下。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Earn Free Cryptos in Web3 - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>How to Earn Free Crypto in the Crypto World - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Every year, the crypto world sees numerous projects that make people around us rich. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a myth; it&amp;rsquo;s real. With minimal investment, you can get lucky and receive free tokens from projects. Compared to active trading, airdrops seem to offer lower risks and potentially higher rewards. So, what are these airdrops and how can you participate in them? Generally, it involves getting involved in the early stages of a project or community and receiving rewards from the project team at little or no cost. However, you need to be familiar with some basics and prepare some essential tools.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>币圈新人如何撸毛，2023撸空投指南</title><link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>币圈每年都有很多项目，让身边人实现暴富神话，是的，不是传说，在几乎没有投入的情况下，简直就是天上撒币一般的幸运，相比交易这种体力活，撸毛似乎是个风险更低，回报有可能更多的行为，具体是什么行为呢？一般来说就是参与项目或社区的早期建设，然后以无成本或低成本获得项目方奖励，当然需要先了解一些基本的知识并准备一些基本工具。&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>