<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto on Welcome to the World of Web3</title>
    <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/tags/crypto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crypto on Welcome to the World of Web3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 19:26:48 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/tags/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IO.NET GPU算力挖矿教程</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/io-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 19:26:48 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/io-net/</guid>
      <description>IO.NET最近显卡资源出租挖矿模式比较火，后续也有空投可能，代币即将上线，今天说一下如何挖矿，首先支持Ubuntu Linux，MacOS和</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiko Airdrop Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid>
      <description>Taiko is a Layer 2 solution based on Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s ZK-Rollup (Type 1 ZK-EVM). It can be considered a competitor to ZKSync. After successful testing in the first two phases, Taiko has now reached the Alpha3 phase, and it&amp;rsquo;s confirmed that tokens will be released in the future. This means that early participants might receive good rewards. In this guide, we will outline the specific steps for interaction, including basic interactions, contract deployment, and setting up nodes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiko 公链交互完全教程[明牌空投]</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid>
      <description>Taiko是基于以太坊的ZK-Rollup (类型1 ZK-EVM)Layer2。算是ZKSync的竞品，经过了前两个阶段的测试，目前来到了Al</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why and How to Diversify Global Asset Allocation</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/asset-allocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:05:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/asset-allocation/</guid>
      <description>Today, I got together with friends and had some insights to share, so let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the topic of global asset allocation. In the past, I simply outlined the concept to my friends, and within a little over a year, without really doing much, our assets appreciated by around 50%. Considering the current overall economic situation, that&amp;rsquo;s quite a decent achievement.&#xA;In today&amp;rsquo;s ever-changing economic landscape, why do we need to engage in global asset allocation?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>为何以及如何做全球资产配置</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/asset-allocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:57:22 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/asset-allocation/</guid>
      <description>今天和朋友聚了一下，有感而发，聊一下全球资产配置这个话题，因为之前只是简单给朋友规划了一下，也就一年多的时间，什么也没干，资产就增值了50%</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open an Account of German Virtual Bank N26</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/n26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:34:53 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/n26/</guid>
      <description>As we all know, in the cryptocurrency world, handling deposits and withdrawals is an essential and often complex matter. Therefore, in the upcoming tutorials, I will be providing a series of guides to help you tackle this issue.&#xA;Today, let&amp;rsquo;s start by taking a look at N26 Bank, a virtual bank that offers streamlined services. We&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the registration and KYC process for N26.&#xA;Step 1: Register and Download the N26 App</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>如何注册德国虚拟银行 N26</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/n26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:21:38 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/n26/</guid>
      <description>如何注册德国虚拟银行 N26 众所周知，在币圈，出入金是一件特别重要的事，而且还挺复杂的，所以呢接下来我会出一系列教程，去帮助大家解决这个问题 今天首</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023年如何投资加密货币 | 完整初学者指南</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/crypto-tutorial-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 01:37:33 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/crypto-tutorial-2023/</guid>
      <description>在web3.0时代，加密货币越来越受到人们的关注，因为它们提供了一种去中心化的、安全的、透明的支付方式。如果您是一个初学者并想了解如何在20</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Web3 for Security</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/web3-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/web3-security/</guid>
      <description>Web3, also known as Web 3.0 or the decentralized web, refers to the next evolution of the internet that is built on decentralized technologies such as blockchain. Web3 is designed to enhance security and privacy by giving users more control over their data and reducing their dependence on centralized intermediaries.&#xA;Here are some ways you can use Web3 for security:&#xA;Use decentralized applications (dApps): Decentralized applications run on the blockchain and are designed to be more secure than traditional web applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Earn Free Cryptos in Web3 - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid>
      <description>How to Earn Free Crypto in the Crypto World - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023&#xA;Every year, the crypto world sees numerous projects that make people around us rich. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a myth; it&amp;rsquo;s real. With minimal investment, you can get lucky and receive free tokens from projects. Compared to active trading, airdrops seem to offer lower risks and potentially higher rewards. So, what are these airdrops and how can you participate in them?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>币圈新人如何撸毛，2023撸空投指南</title>
      <link>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.bitbitking.com/zh-cn/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid>
      <description>币圈每年都有很多项目，让身边人实现暴富神话，是的，不是传说，在几乎没有投入的情况下，简直就是天上撒币一般的幸运，相比交易这种体力活，撸毛似乎</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
