<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto on Welcome to the World of Web3</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/tags/crypto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crypto on Welcome to the World of Web3</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 21:00:49 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/tags/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aleo 零知识证明网络服务器节点搭建教程</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/aleo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 21:00:49 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/aleo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;aleo简介&#34;&gt;Aleo简介&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aleo 致力于通过其创新平台为用户和应用程序开发人员提供前所未有的隐私保护。利用去中心化系统和零知识加密技术，Aleo 实现了网络上用户数据的绝对保密性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IO.NET GPU 显卡算力挖矿教程</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/io-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 19:26:48 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/io-net/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IO.NET最近显卡资源出租挖矿模式比较火，后续也有空投可能，代币即将上线，今天说一下如何挖矿，首先支持Ubuntu Linux，MacOS和Windows操作系统，就以Windows为例讲解具体过程&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiko Airdrop Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Taiko is a Layer 2 solution based on Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s ZK-Rollup (Type 1 ZK-EVM). It can be considered a competitor to ZKSync. After successful testing in the first two phases, Taiko has now reached the Alpha3 phase, and it&amp;rsquo;s confirmed that tokens will be released in the future. This means that early participants might receive good rewards. In this guide, we will outline the specific steps for interaction, including basic interactions, contract deployment, and setting up nodes. By following this tutorial, you should be well-prepared for similar airdrop campaigns in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiko 公链交互完全教程[明牌空投]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/taiko-airdrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 06:40:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/taiko-airdrop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Taiko是基于以太坊的ZK-Rollup (类型1 ZK-EVM)Layer2。算是ZKSync的竞品，经过了前两个阶段的测试，目前来到了Alpha3阶段，确认将来会发布代币，可以说是明牌空投了，所以在早期参与的用户回报应该会不错，这里就给大家整理一下具体的交互步骤，包括常规交互、部署合约和搭建节点，通过这一个教程，以后做这类空投应该也会触类旁通。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why and How to Diversify Global Asset Allocation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/asset-allocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:05:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/asset-allocation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, I got together with friends and had some insights to share, so let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the topic of global asset allocation. In the past, I simply outlined the concept to my friends, and within a little over a year, without really doing much, our assets appreciated by around 50%. Considering the current overall economic situation, that&amp;rsquo;s quite a decent achievement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s ever-changing economic landscape, why do we need to engage in global asset allocation? And how can we effectively allocate our assets to achieve appreciation and preservation in value?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>为何以及如何做全球资产配置</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/asset-allocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:57:22 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/asset-allocation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;今天和朋友聚了一下，有感而发，聊一下全球资产配置这个话题，因为之前只是简单给朋友规划了一下，也就一年多的时间，什么也没干，资产就增值了50%左右，再这样的一个整体经济形势下，应该算是个不错的成绩。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Open an Account of German Virtual Bank N26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/n26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:34:53 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/n26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As we all know, in the cryptocurrency world, handling deposits and withdrawals is an essential and often complex matter. Therefore, in the upcoming tutorials, I will be providing a series of guides to help you tackle this issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, let&amp;rsquo;s start by taking a look at N26 Bank, a virtual bank that offers streamlined services. We&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the registration and KYC process for N26.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Register and Download the N26 App&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>如何注册德国虚拟银行 N26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/n26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:21:38 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/n26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;如何注册德国虚拟银行 N26&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;众所周知，在币圈，出入金是一件特别重要的事，而且还挺复杂的，所以呢接下来我会出一系列教程，去帮助大家解决这个问题&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天首先来看一下这个N26银行，它其实是一个虚拟银行，我们一起看一下N26的注册及KYC流程&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023年如何投资加密货币 | 完整初学者指南</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/crypto-tutorial-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 01:37:33 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/crypto-tutorial-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;在web3.0时代，加密货币越来越受到人们的关注，因为它们提供了一种去中心化的、安全的、透明的支付方式。如果您是一个初学者并想了解如何在2023年投资加密货币，这期视频就是一个非常适合你，简单明了的指南：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Web3 for Security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/web3-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/web3-security/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Web3, also known as Web 3.0 or the decentralized web, refers to the next evolution of the internet that is built on decentralized technologies such as blockchain. Web3 is designed to enhance security and privacy by giving users more control over their data and reducing their dependence on centralized intermediaries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are some ways you can use Web3 for security:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use decentralized applications (dApps): Decentralized applications run on the blockchain and are designed to be more secure than traditional web applications. When you use a dApp, you have control over your data, and it cannot be accessed by a centralized authority. Some popular dApps include MetaMask, MyEtherWallet, and Uniswap.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Earn Free Cryptos in Web3 - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/en/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How to Earn Free Crypto in the Crypto World - A Guide to Airdrops in 2023&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every year, the crypto world sees numerous projects that make people around us rich. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a myth; it&amp;rsquo;s real. With minimal investment, you can get lucky and receive free tokens from projects. Compared to active trading, airdrops seem to offer lower risks and potentially higher rewards. So, what are these airdrops and how can you participate in them? Generally, it involves getting involved in the early stages of a project or community and receiving rewards from the project team at little or no cost. However, you need to be familiar with some basics and prepare some essential tools.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>币圈新人如何撸毛，2023撸空投指南</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/zh-cn/posts/airdrop-tutorial-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;币圈每年都有很多项目，让身边人实现暴富神话，是的，不是传说，在几乎没有投入的情况下，简直就是天上撒币一般的幸运，相比交易这种体力活，撸毛似乎是个风险更低，回报有可能更多的行为，具体是什么行为呢？一般来说就是参与项目或社区的早期建设，然后以无成本或低成本获得项目方奖励，当然需要先了解一些基本的知识并准备一些基本工具。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
